# **Dexter Crago** Software Developer

My Personal Website

in LinkedIn

GitHub 
■ dexter18crago@gmail.com

### Profile

I'm Dexter, a full-stack web developer with a strong grasp of programming fundamentals, lots of experience fixing my own code, and a strong drive to continue learning and improving my skills. Feel free to check out my personal website ♂ to see some of my work and learn more about me and how I can start adding value to your team right away!

#### Education

**Software Development,** The Odin Project

Aug 2023 - May 2024

Project-based learning

**Bachelor of Science,** *Montana State University* 

Aug 2021 - May 2023

**High School Science Education** 

**Bachelor of Science,** University of Montana

Aug 2018 - May 2021

**High School Science Education** 

**High School Diploma,** Big Sky High School

Aug 2014 - Jun 2018

International Baccalaureate Diploma

## Organizations

**Montana Indian Ministries,** Summer Camp Leader

Jun 2015 – present

Co-lead 50+ camp counselors

**Morning Star Elementary School,** *Tech Club Leader* 

Feb 2022 – May 2022

Led a weekly after-school tech club for elementary students





## Professional Experience

**Stevensville High School,** Student Teacher

Jan 2023 - Apr 2023

Responsible for over 100 students

Montana Club, Server

Jun 2015 - Mar 2021

Served at least 100 clients per day

**City Life Community Center,** Youth Worker

Jun 2018 – Jun 2020

Coordinated trips for 20+ students